<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Apk Analyzer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_item_list">Items</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="NA">N/A</string>
    <string name="none">none</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="intro">Analyze your installed apps!</string>

    <string name="all_apps">All apps</string>
    <string name="system_apps">System apps</string>
    <string name="user_apps">User apps</string>
    <string name="app_list_empty">No applications installed</string>

    <string name="general">General</string>
    <string name="certificate">Certificate</string>
    <string name="activities">Activities</string>
    <string name="services">Services</string>
    <string name="content_providers">Content Providers</string>
    <string name="broadcast_receivers">Broadcast Receivers</string>
    <string name="permissions">Used Permissions</string>
    <string name="defined_permissions">Defined Permissions</string>
    <string name="files">Files</string>
    <string name="resources">Resources</string>


    <string name="install_loc_auto">Automatic</string>
    <string name="install_loc_internal_only">Internal storage only</string>
    <string name="install_loc_preffer_external">Preffer external storage</string>
    <string name="install_loc_unspecified">Unspecified</string>


    <string name="application_name">Application name</string>
    <string name="package_name">Package name</string>
    <string name="process_name">Process name</string>
    <string name="version_name">Version name</string>
    <string name="version_code">Version code</string>
    <string name="system_application">System application</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="target_sdk">Target SDK</string>
    <string name="target_version">Target version</string>
    <string name="min_sdk">Min SDK</string>
    <string name="min_version">Min version</string>
    <string name="apk_directory">Apk path</string>
    <string name="data_directory">Data path</string>
    <string name="install_loc">Install location</string>
    <string name="apk_size">Apk size</string>
    <string name="first_install">First install</string>
    <string name="last_update">Last update</string>

    <string name="application_name_description">The name of this application. This name is displayed to users. Internally, Android uses package name attribute as a unique identifier of application. </string>
    <string name="package_name_description">The name of this package. From the Android Manifest tag\'s "name" attribute. The package name serves as a unique identifier for the application. It\'s also the default name for the application process and the default task affinity of an activity.</string>
    <string name="process_name_description">The name of the process this application should run in. From the "process" attribute or, if not set, the same as package name.</string>
    <string name="version_name_description">The version number shown to users. The attribute has no other purpose than to be displayed to users. The Version code attribute holds the significant version number used internally.</string>
    <string name="version_code_description">An internal version number. This number is used only to determine whether one version is more recent than another, with higher numbers indicating more recent versions. This is not the version number shown to users; that number is set by the Version name attribute.</string>
    <string name="system_application_description">If set tot rue, this application is installed in the device\'s system image.</string>
    <string name="description_description">The application\'s description specified by application developer.</string>
    <string name="target_sdk_description">A number designating the Android API Level that the application targets. This attribute informs the system that application is tested against the target version and the system should not enable any compatibility behaviors to maintain app\'s forward-compatibility with the target version. The application is still able to run on older versions (down to Min Sdk Version).</string>
    <string name="target_version_description">Value of Target SDK attribute resolved to the version of Android</string>
    <string name="min_sdk_description">A number designating the minimum Android API Level required for the application to run. The Android system will prevent the user from installing the application if the system\'s API Level is lower than the value specified in this attribute. Google Play uses the this attributes to filter app from devices that do not meet it\'s platform version requirements.</string>
    <string name="min_version_description">Value of Min SDK attribute resolved to the version of Android</string>
    <string name="apk_directory_description">Android applications are distributed as an Android Application Packages (APK). Once installed, APK file is saved in storage. This attribute represents path to APK file of given application.</string>
    <string name="data_directory_description">Full path to the default directory assigned to the package for its persistent data.</string>
    <string name="install_loc_description">The default install location for the application. The following values are accepted:\n\n<b>Internal Only</b> - The application must be installed on the internal device storage only. If this is set, the application will never be installed on the external storage. If the internal storage is full, then the system will not install the application. This is also the default behavior. \n\n<b>Auto</b> - The application may be installed on the external storage, but the system will install the application on the internal storage by default. If the internal storage is full, then the system will install it on the external storage. Once installed, the user can move the application to either internal or external storage through the system settings. \n\n<b>Prefer External</b> - The application prefers to be installed on the external storage (SD card). There is no guarantee that the system will honor this request. The application might be installed on internal storage if the external media is unavailable or full. Once installed, the user can move the application to either internal or external storage through the system settings.</string>
    <string name="apk_size_description">Size of APK file</string>
    <string name="first_install_description">The time at which the app was first installed.</string>
    <string name="last_update_description">The time at which the app was last updated.</string>

    <string name="sign_algorithm">Sign algorithm</string>
    <string name="start_date">Valid from</string>
    <string name="end_date">Valid to</string>
    <string name="public_key_md5">Public key MD5</string>
    <string name="cert_md5">Certificate MD5</string>
    <string name="serial_number">Serial number</string>
    <string name="issuer_name">Issuer name</string>
    <string name="issuer_organization">Issuer organization</string>
    <string name="issuer_country">Issuer country</string>
    <string name="subject_name">Subject name</string>
    <string name="subject_organization">Subject organization</string>
    <string name="subject_country">Subject country</string>

    <string name="sign_algorithm_description">The signature algorithm name for the certificate signature algorithm. An example is the string \"SHA256withRSA\"</string>
    <string name="start_date_description">Start of validity period of the certificate.</string>
    <string name="end_date_description">End of validity period of the certificate.</string>
    <string name="public_key_md5_description">MD5 hash of public key of the certificate.</string>
    <string name="cert_md5_description">MD5 hash of the certificate.</string>
    <string name="serial_number_description">Serial Number value from the certificate. The serial number is an integer assigned by the certification authority to each certificate. It must be unique for each certificate issued by a given CA (i.e., the issuer name and serial number identify a unique certificate).</string>
    <string name="issuer_name_description">Name of issuer of the certificate</string>
    <string name="issuer_organization_description">Name of organization of issuer of the certificate</string>
    <string name="issuer_country_description">Country of issuer of the certificate</string>
    <string name="subject_name_description">Name of subject of the certificate</string>
    <string name="subject_organization_description">Name of organization of subject of the certificate</string>
    <string name="subject_country_description">Country of subject of the certificate</string>

    <string name="all_drawables">Total drawables</string>
    <string name="different_drawables">Different drawables</string>
    <string name="png_drawables">png drawables</string>
    <string name="nine_patch_drawables">9.png drawables</string>
    <string name="jpg_drawables">jpg drawables</string>
    <string name="gif_drawables">gif drawables</string>
    <string name="xml_drawables">xml drawables</string>
    <string name="ldpi_drawables">ldpi drawables</string>
    <string name="mdpi_drawables">png drawables</string>
    <string name="hdpi_drawables">mdpi drawables</string>
    <string name="xhdpi_drawables">xhdpi drawables</string>
    <string name="xxhdpi_drawables">xxhdpi drawables</string>
    <string name="xxxhdpi_drawables">xxxhdpi drawables</string>
    <string name="nodpi_drawables">nodpi drawables</string>
    <string name="tvdpi_drawables">tvdpi drawables</string>
    <string name="all_layouts">All layouts</string>
    <string name="different_layouts">Different layouts</string>

    <string name="all_drawables_description">Total number of drawables contained in APK file. This includes all files in /res/drawable directory. Files from support libraries are included as well. If drawable is provided multiple times, e.g. in different resolution, it is counted multiple times.</string>
    <string name="different_drawables_description">Number of logically unique drawables contained in APK file. Files from support libraries are included as well. If drawable is provided multiple times, e.g. in different resolution, it is counted only once.</string>
    <string name="png_drawables_description">Number of png drawables included in APK file.</string>
    <string name="nine_patch_drawables_description">Number of nine patch (9.png) drawables included in APK file. A nine patch drawable graphic is a stretchable bitmap image that you can use as the background of a view. Android automatically resizes the graphic to accommodate the contents of the view. </string>
    <string name="jpg_drawables_description">Number of jpg drawables included in APK file.</string>
    <string name="gif_drawables_description">Number of gif drawables included in APK file.</string>
    <string name="xml_drawables_description">Number of xml drawables included in APK file. Xml drawables are marker files containing data about shapes etc.</string>
    <string name="ldpi_drawables_description">Number of drawables optimized for screens with low pixel density ~120dpi</string>
    <string name="mdpi_drawables_description">Number of drawables optimized for screens with medium pixel density ~160dpi</string>
    <string name="hdpi_drawables_description">Number of drawables optimized for screens with high pixel density ~240dpi</string>
    <string name="xhdpi_drawables_description">Number of drawables optimized for screens with extra high pixel density ~320dpi</string>
    <string name="xxhdpi_drawables_description">Number of drawables optimized for screens with extra extra high pixel density ~480dpi</string>
    <string name="xxxhdpi_drawables_description">Number of drawables optimized for screens with extra extra extra high pixel density ~640dpi</string>
    <string name="nodpi_drawables_description">Number of drawables for all densities. These are density-independent resources. The system does not scale resources tagged with this qualifier, regardless of the current screen\'s density.</string>
    <string name="tvdpi_drawables_description">Resources for screens somewhere between mdpi and hdpi; approximately 213dpi. This is not considered a "primary" density group. It is mostly intended for televisions and most apps shouldn\'t need it—providing mdpi and hdpi resources is sufficient for most apps and the system will scale them as appropriate.</string>
    <string name="all_layouts_description">Total number of layouts contained in APK file. This includes all files in /res/layouts directory. Files from support libraries are included as well. If layout is provided multiple times, e.g. one layout name for two layouts - one in landscape and other in portrait modus, it is counted multiple times.</string>
    <string name="different_layouts_description">Number of logically unique layouts contained in APK file. Files from support libraries are included as well. If layout is provided multiple times, e.g. one layout name for two layouts - one in landscape and other in portrait modus, it is counted only once.</string>

    <string name="activity_label">Label</string>
    <string name="activity_parent">Parent</string>
    <string name="activity_permission">Permission</string>

    <string name="service_exported">Exported</string>
    <string name="service_stop_with_task">Stop with task</string>
    <string name="service_single_user">Single user</string>
    <string name="service_isolated_process">Isolated process</string>
    <string name="service_external_service">External</string>

    <string name="service_permission_description">Optional name of a permission required to be able to access this Service.</string>
    <string name="service_exported_description">If true, service may be called by another activity.</string>
    <string name="service_stop_with_task_description">The service will automatically be stopped by the system if the user removes a task that is rooted in one of the application\'s activities.</string>
    <string name="service_single_user_description">Single instance of the service will run for all users on the device.</string>
    <string name="service_isolated_process_description">The service will run in its own isolated process.</string>
    <string name="service_external_service_description">The service can be bound and run in the calling application\'s package, rather than the package in which it is declared.</string>

    <string name="provider_authority">Authority</string>
    <string name="provider_read_permission">Read permission</string>
    <string name="provider_write_permission">Write permission</string>
    <string name="provider_exported">Exported</string>

    <string name="provider_authority_description">Authorities that identify data offered by the content provider. Data offered by this content provider are published under this identification.</string>
    <string name="provider_read_permission_description">Optional permission required for read-only access this content provider.</string>
    <string name="provider_write_permission_description">Optional permission required for read/write access this content provider.</string>
    <string name="provider_exported_description">Whether the content provider is available for other applications to use:\n\ntrue: The provider is available to other applications. Any application can use the provider\'s content URI to access it, subject to the permissions specified for the provider. \n\nfalse: The provider is not available to other applications. Set android:exported="false" to limit access to the provider to your applications. Only applications that have the same user ID (UID) as the provider will have access to it.</string>

    <string name="receiver_permission">Permission</string>
    <string name="receiver_exported">Exported</string>

    <string name="receiver_permission_description">The name of a permission that broadcasters must have to send a message to the broadcast receiver. If this attribute is not set, the permission set by the application element\'s permission attribute applies to the broadcast receiver. If neither attribute is set, the receiver is not protected by a permission.</string>
    <string name="receiver_exported_descritpion">Whether or not the broadcast receiver can receive messages from sources outside its application - \"yes\" if it can, and \"no\" if not. If no, the only messages the broadcast receiver can receive are those sent by components of the same application or applications with the same user ID.</string>

    <string name="arithmetic_mean">Arithmetic mean</string>
    <string name="median">Median</string>
    <string name="max">Max</string>
    <string name="min">Min</string>
    <string name="variance">Variance</string>
    <string name="deviation">Deviation</string>

    <string-array name="android_versions">
        <item>item</item>
        <item>Android 1</item>
        <item>Android 1.1 Petit Four</item>
        <item>Android 1.5 Cupcake</item>
        <item>Android 1.6 Donut</item>
        <item>Android 2.0 Eclair</item>
        <item>Android 2.0.1 Eclair</item>
        <item>Android 2.1 Eclair</item>
        <item>Android 2.2 Froyo</item>
        <item>Android 2.3 Gingerbread</item>
        <item>Android 2.3.3 Gingerbread</item>
        <item>Android 3.0 Honeycomb</item>
        <item>Android 3.1 Honeycomb</item>
        <item>Android 3.2 Honeycomb</item>
        <item>Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich</item>
        <item>Android 4.0.3 Ice Cream Sandwich</item>
        <item>Android 4.1 Jelly Bean</item>
        <item>Android 4.2 Jelly Bean</item>
        <item>Android 4.3 Jelly Bean</item>
        <item>Android 4.4 KitKat</item>
        <item>Android 4.4W KitKat</item>
        <item>Android 5.0 Lollipop</item>
        <item>Android 5.1.1 Lollipop</item>
        <item>Android 6.0 Marshmallow</item>
        <item>Android 7.0 Nougat</item>
        <item>Android 7.1.2 Nougat</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
